Ever wondered what actually works when it comes to coding agents.
Hi my name is Maria Gorinova and I'm an AI Researcher here at Tessl.
I will be giving a webinar together with our Head of Product and Design,
Dru Knox on the 19th of March at 4 p.m.
UK time.
With traditional software you can run tests, you can run static analysis.
But when it comes to agents, things are entirely different.
The skill that you just wrote
might work well for one example and then completely fail the next one.
Agents require a different way of thinking.
In this session we will walk through designing tests for your skills
that give you real insights What evaluation criteria should you use?
How do you assess if your changes will work reliably?
And how do you use some of these to continuously improve your agent's
performance?
If you are an engineer, a researcher or a technical leader building with agents
and you want to make decisions grounded in data, this one is for you.
It's free to attend.
Follow the link to register.
We hope to see you there.